因此，除了你的工作生活，你还有很多方法可以在你的个人生活中使用ChatGPT，还有一些有趣的方法。
So in addition to your work life, there's a lot of ways you can use ChatGPT in your personal life, too, and some fun ways to do it.
我们来看看其中的一些。
And we're going to look at a few of them here.
我们要看的是，这是真的，我真的必须这样做。
One we're going to look at is, and this is true, I had to really do this.
我需要给我妻子一个礼物的主意，她刚刚真正开始园艺，对园艺很陌生，真的很喜欢园艺。
I needed a gift idea for my wife, and she had just really got into gardening, is new into gardening, really into gardening.
我对园艺一无所知。
And I have no idea about gardening.
我不知道该给她买什么。
I have no idea what to buy her.
我会给她买一把耙子或什么可怕的东西，也许是一些
I'd buy her a rake or something terrible, maybe some
你知道谁知道像一个小洞或一些无聊而愚蠢的东西，所以我不知道该怎么纠正她，但我在看一些视频和东西，她在说，哦，有非常酷的日本园艺东西，这就是我所知道的，对了，有很酷的日本园林东西，我该用这个权利去哪里，所以我去聊天GPT，对了在这里日本园艺刀或日本园艺工具作为礼物
you know who knows like a little hole or something that's just boring and dumb so I didn't know what to get her right but I was watching some videos and things and she's talking about how like oh there's really cool Japanese gardening stuff and that's all I know right there's cool Japanese gardening stuff where do I go with that right so I go to chat GPT right so let's say I go to GPT and I put in here Japanese gardening knife or Japanese gardening tools as a gift
正确的
right?
让我们把它放进去，看看我是否可以开始缩小范围，以获得一些东西的想法。
Let's put that in and see if I can start narrowing this down to get some ideas of stuff.
它们可以是深思熟虑和实用的，然后这里有一些东西，对吧？
They can be thoughtful and practical and then here's some stuff, right?
There's bonsai scissors, a hori-hori knife.
这看起来很有趣。
This looks interesting.
事实上，我发现这是一种用于种植、除草和划分植物的多功能工具，因为她总是抱怨
That's actually what I found was it was versatile tool to use for planting, weeding, and dividing plants because she's always complaining about
你知道她必须做的所有工作，为她的植物放一晚你知道的东西，你知道是给它们除草还是放新的——所有这些听起来像是这把灰色的刀可以做任何事情，但我不知道它给了我一个关于什么是灰色的刀的小描述，但我想知道更多，就像你知道的那样，也许我可以输入并深入了解，看看这是不是合适的礼物，就像你知道你怎么用一样
you know all the work she has to do to put in you know stuff for a night for her plants and you know whether it's weeding them or putting in new ones all this sounds like this hoary hoary knife can do do everything but i have no idea it gives me a little description on what a hoary hoary knife is but i'd like to know more like you know like maybe i could type in and go deeper see if this is the right gift like you know um how do you use
我只是想看看，这是送给我妻子的合适礼物吗？
I'm just really trying to see, is this the right gift for my wife, right?
然后在这里进行更多的讨论，并进行更详细的分析。
And so then talks more here and breaks it out in more detail.
所以，如果我把它给她，她说，好吧，这是什么，我可以说，哦，这是一把角质的刀。
So then if I, when I give it to her and she says, well, what's this, I can say, oh, it's a horny, horny knife.
这真的很好
It's really good for like
种植。
planting.
种植真的很棒。
It's really great with planting.
你也可以用它除草。
You can also use it for weeding.
你有植物要分吗？
Do you got plants to divide?
它真的很擅长。
It's really good at that.
我喜欢，我认为它也非常适合种植土壤或移植，你知道，把植物移过来。
I like, I think it's really great for cultivating soil too or transplanting, you know, moving plants over.
我的意思是，我只是真的很关心你，你知道，我让我妻子和我真的很想了解你在做什么。
I mean, I just really care about you, you know, I let my wife and I really want to understand what you're doing.
And so I think this Hori-Hori knife,
你知道圣诞快乐或生日快乐，对吧，这是她的生日礼物对吧，然后我听起来真的很聪明，因为现在我知道了Hori Hori刀，所以我给她买了一把Hori Hori-刀，现在我不知道的是，如果你看一把Hori-Hori刀你知道这些看起来很危险，对吧它们很锋利，它们有剃刀边缘，它们有锯齿边缘深度和诸如此类的东西我的意思是这些东西对我来说就像是杀害丈夫的凶手
you know Merry Christmas or happy birthday here you go right it was her birthday gift right and then I sound really smart because now I know about Hori-Hori knives so I got her a Hori-Hori knife now what I didn't know is if you look at a Hori-Hori knife you know these are gonna look like they're dangerous right they're sharp edge they got a razor edge they've got a serrated edge it's got you know depth and all that kind of stuff on it too I mean these these things look like husband killers to me
我不知道这是否是最好的礼物。不要让她生气，因为霍伊刀可以对着我，而不是对着植物。但有一个想法，我只是为了好玩，我用了聊天GBT，我给了她一份很棒的礼物和一份意想不到的礼物。你知道，你知道，我没有告诉她这是聊天GBT实际上是我的领导者，她说，哦，这是喷气GBT的东西，嗯？
I don't know if this is the best gift don't make her mad because the hoi hoi knife could be turned on me and not on the plants But here was an idea where just for fun I was I used chat GBT and I got her a great gift and an unexpected gift You know, you know, I didn't tell her it's chat GBT actually leader I did and she's like oh that's jet GBT stuff, huh?
好吧，哦，但她仍然喜欢她的角质刀和
Okay, oh, but she still loves her horny horny knife and
希望我的发音是正确的，如果我不抱歉的话，我不是一个正确的园丁，但我只是做了一点，比如哦，她对某种日本园艺工具感兴趣，从那以后我可以得到一份礼物，但我可以从园艺工具开始，你知道，可以从更广泛的角度开始，但通过缩小范围并提供聊天GBT好信息，我能够得到一份很好的礼物来自我妻子，所以这也是一个有趣的方式，你也可以使用聊天GBT。
and hopefully I'm pronouncing that correctly if I'm not sorry I'm not a gardener right but I just do a little bit like oh she was interested in some type of Japanese tools for gardening from that I could get to a gift ideas but I could start about just gardening tools you know could start a broader that way but by narrowing it in and giving chat GBT good information I was able to get a nice gift from my wife so that's a fun way you can use chat GBT too.